And now, please welcome to The O2 Arena, London — Team World!
现在，伦敦O2体育馆，有请世界队！
Leading up the players, a two-time champion in his breakout 2026 season,
率先出场的，是在2026年迎来突破、两度夺冠的他，
including a stunning title run in Hamburg. Welcome Ignacio Buse!
其中包括汉堡站的惊艳夺冠。欢迎布塞！
Now on the black court, the Peruvian makes his Laver Cup debut as the Team World alternate.
踏上黑色球场，这位秘鲁人以世界队替补身份首次亮相拉沃尔杯。
A two-time champion in 2026, winning at home in Buenos Aires
2026年两度夺冠：先在主场布宜诺斯艾利斯称王，
before lifting the trophy at Queen's Club. Welcome Francisco Cerundolo!
又在女王俱乐部捧杯。欢迎塞伦多洛！
The Argentine star is making his fourth Laver Cup appearance.
这位阿根廷球星第四次出战拉沃尔杯。
A champion in Hong Kong this season, bringing incredible shot-making,
本赛季香港站冠军，击球天马行空，
creativity and unpredictability to the court. Welcome Alexander Bublik!
充满创造力，让人捉摸不透。欢迎布勃利克！
He's from Kazakhstan and making his Laver Cup debut.
他来自哈萨克斯坦，首次出战拉沃尔杯。
One of America's most consistent young stars, continuing another stellar season.
美国最稳定的年轻球星之一，又一个出色的赛季。
Welcome to The O2, Brandon Nakashima!
欢迎来到 O2，中岛布兰登！
Now stepping onto the black court in London for his Team World debut.
踏上伦敦的黑色球场，他首次代表世界队出战。
One of the brightest young talents in the game, the Australian Open quarterfinalist
网坛最耀眼的年轻天才之一，澳网1/4决赛选手、
and a semifinalist in Montreal. Please welcome Learner Tien!
蒙特利尔站半决赛选手。有请勒纳·钱！
The young American is also making his Laver Cup debut.
这位美国小将同样是首次出战拉沃尔杯。
A champion in Washington this summer and a Wimbledon quarterfinalist.
今夏华盛顿站冠军，温网1/4决赛选手。
He's already helped Team World lift the Laver Cup trophy three times.
他已经3次帮助世界队捧起拉沃尔杯。
From the United States, it's Taylor Fritz!
来自美国——弗里茨！
Back to compete for his sixth Laver Cup appearance.
第六次出战拉沃尔杯。
A Rotterdam champion this year and an Australian Open quarterfinalist,
今年鹿特丹站冠军、澳网1/4决赛选手，
bringing his trademark speed and intensity back to Team World.
把招牌的速度与拼劲带回世界队。
From Australia, please welcome Alex de Minaur!
来自澳大利亚，有请德米纳尔！
A two-time Laver Cup champion, he's back for his third appearance.
两度随队赢下拉沃尔杯，第三次出战。
A swashbuckling net rusher with a booming kick serve
上网凶悍，踢式发球威力十足，
and back-to-back US Open champion in 1997 and 1998.
1997、1998年美网两连冠。
Welcome Patrick Rafter!
欢迎拉夫特！
The Aussie legend returns to Team World as vice-captain.
这位澳洲传奇以副队长身份回到世界队。
One of only nine men in history to complete the career Grand Slam.
史上仅有9位完成职业全满贯的男子球员之一。
The man who led Team World to victory last year.
去年带领世界队夺冠的人。
London, please welcome Andre Agassi!
伦敦，有请阿加西！
The American superstar returns as your Team World captain.
这位美国巨星再度出任世界队队长。
London, let's hear it for Team World!
伦敦，为世界队欢呼吧！
And now, please welcome to The O2 Arena — Team Europe!
现在，O2体育馆，有请欧洲队！
Leading up the players, this British breakout star produced a sensational run
率先出场的这位英国新星，打出了一段惊艳的征程，
all the way to the Wimbledon semifinals. Welcome Arthur Fery!
一路打进温网半决赛。欢迎费里！
Now at The O2, he makes his Laver Cup debut as the Team Europe alternate.
在 O2，他以欧洲队替补身份首次亮相拉沃尔杯。
One of Team Europe's most experienced competitors,
欧洲队最有经验的球员之一，
with six Laver Cup match wins already to his name.
已经在拉沃尔杯拿下6场胜利。
From Norway, it's Casper Ruud!
来自挪威——鲁德！
He's back in blue for an incredible sixth consecutive appearance.
他再穿蓝衣，已是连续第六次出战。
A champion in Auckland this season, with semifinal runs in Doha and at Roland Garros.
本赛季奥克兰站冠军，多哈站和法网都打进半决赛。
From Czechia, welcome Jakub Mensik!
来自捷克，欢迎门西克！
He's back in blue with Team Europe for his second appearance.
他第二次身披蓝衣为欧洲队出战。
One of the breakthrough players of 2026,
2026年的突破之星之一，
capturing his maiden ATP title in Marrakech.
在马拉喀什拿下个人首个 ATP 冠军。
From Spain, welcome Rafael Jodar!
来自西班牙，欢迎霍达尔！
Now stepping onto the black court for his Laver Cup debut with Team Europe.
踏上黑色球场，他首次代表欧洲队出战拉沃尔杯。
The Italian has enjoyed a breakthrough season,
这位意大利人迎来突破赛季，
powering his way to his first Grand Slam final at Roland Garros.
一路杀进个人首个大满贯决赛——法网。
Please welcome Flavio Cobolli!
有请科博利！
He's back in blue with Team Europe for his second appearance.
他第二次身披蓝衣为欧洲队出战。
Already a career Grand Slam champion,
早已完成职业全满贯，
the Spanish superstar continues to add extraordinary achievements to his incredible young career.
这位西班牙巨星还在为年轻的职业生涯不断添上非凡成就。
London, make some noise for Carlos Alcaraz!
伦敦，为阿尔卡拉斯欢呼吧！
A Laver Cup champion in Berlin, he's back in blue for his third appearance with Team Europe.
柏林那届拉沃尔杯冠军成员，第三次身披蓝衣为欧洲队出战。
A two-time Grand Slam champion in 2026, conquering Roland Garros and the US Open,
2026年两夺大满贯，征服法网与美网，
and a five-time champion with Team Europe. From Germany, say hello to Alexander Zverev!
5次随欧洲队夺冠。来自德国，欢迎兹维列夫！
Sasha returns to Laver Cup for a record seventh appearance.
萨沙第七次出战拉沃尔杯，创下纪录。
A four-time Wimbledon semifinalist and winner of 15 combined ATP Tour titles
4次打进温网半决赛，单双打合计15个 ATP 巡回赛冠军，
across an outstanding career. London, please welcome back Tim Henman!
生涯辉煌。伦敦，欢迎亨曼回来！
The British tennis legend returns as Team Europe vice-captain.
这位英国网球传奇以欧洲队副队长身份回归。
The 1983 Roland Garros champion, with 23 singles and 16 doubles titles
1983年法网冠军，单打23冠、双打16冠，
across an incredible career spanning two decades.
职业生涯横跨20年。
London, please welcome Yannick Noah,
伦敦，有请诺阿，
leading the blue side for the second time. He's your Team Europe captain!
第二次率领蓝军。他就是欧洲队队长！
London, let's hear it one more time for Team Europe!
伦敦，再为欧洲队欢呼一次！
Ladies and gentlemen, the Laver Cup is named in honor of Australian Rod Laver,
女士们先生们，拉沃尔杯以澳大利亚人罗德·拉沃尔的名字命名，
who won all four major titles in the same calendar year, in 1962 and 1969.
他在1962年和1969年两度在同一年包揽四大满贯。
The latter remains the only time a man has done so in the Open Era.
后一次至今仍是公开赛年代唯一一位做到的男子球员。
London, please welcome to The O2 Arena — Mr. Rod Laver!
伦敦，有请罗德·拉沃尔先生！